Are you ready?
Because I am.
Today we're doing polls.
That's right, we're going to Poland and we're doing those people.
No, you're gonna vote on what's next.
And then after I lose or win, we're gonna vote again.
Isn't that a good plan?
Oh,
I know what I'm voting.
Okay, what if your option isn't on the list?
Huh?
Thought about that?
Okay, are you ready?
We're apparently my content does not meet guidelines.
Uh, what?
Okay, let me try this.
There you go.
Let's see what the answer's gonna be.
What is it gonna be?
I apparently I couldn't write a sasyl.
That's against guidelines on Twitch.
You cannot write a sasyl.
I had to misspell it.
I'm kidding.
Of course.
Come on.
We're gonna do a proper poll here, but I like that the first one got the most votes there.
Nice.
New poll.
Actually, what's on the menu?
Let's say, uh, random heart, random greed, uh, challenge.
And yeah, that's it.
Go.
One minute.
Let's see it.
You gotta vote fast.
And of course, within all of these, we're gonna be doing all kinds of things that I've planned anyway.
Today, we're not following a script.
We're going to totally freestyle.
Nothing is scripted today, which means anything can happen.
Man, I want to play 1942 now, actually.
We should all jump into one server.
I'm gonna jump into a plane and I'm gonna kick all of your asses.
Okay.
55% is on random heart.
That is the clear winner.
Random greed is left in the dust.
We're gonna vote again later, but for now, this is what we do.
Here we go.
I'm gonna actually turn this off.
Yeah.
And boom.
Nice.
Okay.
Random heart.
Who am I?
Wait, minus one win streak, guys.
That's so embarrassing.
We can't let that stand.
We can't let it stand.
Uh, I almost clicked enter just now.
We're going on random.
Here we go.
Oh, what are we getting?
Judas.
All right.
That's fine.
That's gonna be a tough one, but you know, it'll be a good warm up session.
I'm ready for it.
Obviously, we're gonna go as slow as a turtle with this guy.
Slow and meticulous is the plan.
Okay.
We're gonna pray to get some health upgrades.
Uh, interesting room.
Not really a problem, though.
The gym is active, guys.
I forgot I did that.
Nice.
That has to be a good sign, right?
It has to be a wonderful sign.
We're gonna win all the runs today.
I can feel it in my bones.
A lucky penny.
Wait a minute.
Uh, is that a new one?
Because I thought it was a trinket and I can't see my trinket.
Well, we got luck.
That's cool.
I think that may have been a new item we unlocked.
I do remember something about a penny.
Last time.
From greed mode.
Okay.
No tilted rocks yet.
Don't worry, I'm gonna tilt the rocks.
Oh, god.
Man, this guy is going nuts.
I lost my half blue heart, which is a real tragedy.
That's for you.
Special delivery.
We're getting good amounts of bombs here.
No keys, though.
I don't need keys.
Not when the door is open.
No!
The worst item in the game.
Maybe followed by sprinkler as the second worst.
Uh, let me see.
Grants and orbiting top familiar that blocks enemy shots and deals contact damage.
Significantly increases speed.
The top spin speed and contact damage while the active item button is held.
Uh-huh.
Got it.
This item's charge depletes gradually.
Recharges automatically.
All right, let me see here.
I mean, maybe...
Not really.
I'm gonna do this!
I don't trust myself.
That's right, ya boys using actives.
I know some of you have been complaining about me not using my items, but don't worry.
I'm saving them for a rainy day.
It's all calculated.
You think I don't know I'm not reusing them?
It's on purpose.
Give me that.
Sick!
Not that I needed that, but wait a minute.
Two treasure rooms?
Am I losing my mind?
What's happening right now?
Why is this a thing?
What?
Why is there a second?
Oh, the Bible!
I can buy it!
Dude, I gotta go with that.
I'm sorry, Belial.
I'm taking the Bible.
I have... Ooh!
I have abandoned the ways of the Angelism.
Enjoyer.
Kill him.
Nice.
That was a little bit scary.
Oh, man.
Oh, this is... That's not that bad, actually.
Money and key.
No tilted rocks.
Uh, you know what?
I'm not done exploring.
What if we find more blue hearts, right?
Wait, have I even taken damage?
Yeah, I took the half blue damage.
I was about to say I kind of want to try and get perfection.
How am I doing it?
How am I able to be this good?
Insanity.
Wait, was that a tilted rock?
No.
Okay, uh, this way.
Sup, man?
Oh, hey, yo, yo.
You want to step on this, uh, holy water?
Come here.
I guess they're jumping over it.
Also, did that holy water damage?
Uh, dealing damage and spawning a pool of creep that petrifies, right?
Right.
The petrification.
Man, that is actually pretty good.
Luring enemies into that, you know?
It's solid play.
Nice.
I could go in there.
I'm going to go in there.
You may say, why would you do that?
Because you have some little HP and my answer is because I'm good at the game.
Damn, no blue hearts.
Dude, yeah.
Oh, this is the best day ever.
These pills are out of control.
Now we grab this heart.
Wow.
I feel like at this point, maybe I shouldn't even eat more pills because I already got the good ones, right?
Chances of getting bad ones now are pretty high.
Okay.
This is actually the strategy.
And if you get a lot of bad pills in the beginning, you know you just want to keep eating pills, right?
Because now the bad pills are gone.
Only the good ones are left.
Okay.
I didn't mean to throw it that way.
No.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Get petrified, nerd.
There we go.
Man, the holy water.
Uh, right rage.
I thought it was synth oil.
Speed and range.
Wait, what am I hearing?
Oh, there's another boss room.
I was like, wait a minute.
I hear a boss.
Uh, yeah, give me that.
That's good.
Uh, okay.
Ready to go.
I'm ready, boss.
Stephen Seagal.
And it's Jujitsu.
Why didn't he get petrified?
I feel cheated.
Yeah.
Come this way.
You like that?
That was so smart.
Oh, wow.
This guy's flying, so he's not actually going to walk into this, unfortunately.
I don't think.
Yeah, no.
Weird that he got petrified before, though.
Maybe because his father got petrified, then he also got petrified.
Oh, try to juke me.
Clever girl.
Little Stephen.
Yeah, I like it.
No devil shenanigans.
That's okay.
We're going full angel.
I have decided.
It's full angel time.
Also, I am 100% demon now, and I also got a green effect on me.
Why do I have a green skin?
Mine ork now?
Like, hello, this holy water is out of control.
I think I've been sleeping on that.
Nice.
Should I... I am actually going to save my...
Wait a minute, this door's open, and there's no blue fires around.
Unless this is not the same room that I saw last time with the blue fire.
That one had a boss symbol on it, so it could be different.
Ah, but wait, I don't want to do it if I don't have a key.
I'm good.
Yeah, get petrified, nerd.
Come here.
Why didn't he get petrified?
Hello?
I feel like I got scammed just now.
You're going to come over here and get petrified.
There we go.
Good stuff.
There's a key.
I'm in a coin.
Thanks.
I can also fly, remember, if I need to.
Whoa!
I'm kind of throwing.
I'm actually kind of in trouble here.
Shit.
I
can't even look where I'm shooting.
I just need to dodge projectiles right now.
Oh, scary.
Definitely getting in there.
I could have flown, but nah, saving it.
Um, I'm going to blow you up.
Oh, that was sick.
Nice, totally worth.
Make it all the right decisions.
Good.
Dude, I have pretty good range.
Nine range already.
Holy crap.
I be rich.
I may actually, I'm going to fly here.
So I can grab this, that, and the battery.
Beautiful play.
Good.
Now we're going to go slow on these guys.
Low and slow.
Nice.
Can I petrify him?
Yep.
The Book of Sin.
We're going to get to three out of three!
Bookworm!
Now we shoot two tiers sometimes.
Nice.
Maybe I'll come back to that.
Okay, I'm rich, so definitely going to spend some money.
Wait, school back!
Haha, we're taking both books, baby.
Absolutely.
Uh, this is also a jar.
I'm also going to take this.
And that's it.
Let's get the other book.
Yeah!
Oh, that's dope.
That's really nice.
Look at the little cute bag we have.
Let's go to school.
Uh, get petrified!
Hey, come this way!
Yeah.
I mean, Judas is doing pretty good damage.
Like, if you can, you know, not get hit, it's actually pretty good.
And if you find HP like I did, of course.
Good stuff.
No tilted rocks.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Stay in the creep puddle.
I'm glad the holy water doesn't break when it hits a wall.
Oh, no, not these guys.
Just going to hide out a bit here while they go crazy.
There's the boss.
Oh, dude, we should totally do speedruns today.
If I get a good character for that, you know, we're totally doing it.
I want to do the 15 waves, get a free frickin...
Especially because it spawns blue hearts as you go.
Like, it's not even that bad, you know?
Five bombs, do I want to...
Oh, I definitely see a secret room area.
Right here, I guarantee it.
Oh!
Okay, maybe overhear them.
I don't guarantee this one.
I give up.
I am not good at finding these.
It's like saying I'm not good at gambling.
Okay, my creep versus your creep.
I'm just going to wait for my...
Yeah, there we go.
Enjoy!
Uh-oh.
No problem.
We got it.
Synth oil, eh?
Not bad.
Moving on.
This is one of my favorite areas.
Flooded caves.
It's just such a vibe down here.
Oh, I should also be using this.
Almost forgot I had that.
Doi-yoi-yoi.
Dude, I have good damage.
Okay, I did say I didn't want to, you know, eat more pills.
I'm actually not going to eat it.
That's right.
We're leaving it.
Uh, drops.
Okay, listen.
We're gonna go full pills.
It's okay.
Uh-oh.
Yo, okay, we're good.
Definitely going pills.
Oish.
Come to me.
Yeah, walk.
Yeah!
I got hit.
That's unreal.
So sad.
Oi-yoi-yoi-yoi-yoi-yoi-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo-yo.
Okay, we gotta light him up.
Light him up, light him up, light him up.
Don't panic.
It's okay.
Line him up.
Wonderful.
What is it?
Shit.
Okay, we had so much range anyway.
It was worth it.
Oh, I missed the shop.
Oh, god.
Oh!
Fuck!
Let me go to the shop.
Another pill.
Nice.
What's that one?
It's only seven.
Never-ending stores.
Upon purchasing a shop item and new item immediately takes its place.
Prices incrementally increase.
All right.
I guess it didn't work for this one because I, you know, it's the one I picked up.
That's cool.
Now we just got to find a bunch of money.
It
doesn't seem to be one of those
No.
Okay.
Oh, man.
Give me a heart.
Okay.
Oh, I almost got hit there.
Oh, we have a half a heart back here.
I'm definitely grabbing.
Oh, don't step on the spikes.
Here.
And let's look for secrets.
I think, potentially, we have something here.
Good.
Now, where's the other one?
Maybe it's right here.
No.
Okay.
Could be.
Actually, if you want to be like totally safe, you know, and what's the word for it?
If you want to make absolutely sure, you want to check all the surrounding rooms, right?
Because if there's a lake here, like you can't have a hole because you can't walk through a lake.
Why?
Yeah, get petrified, nerds.
So good.
Let's see here.
Like, this is a possibility now.
I'm gonna say yes.
No, fine.
I'm actually kind of scared of this room.
Oh, man.
Fuck, man.
I'm never ready for that projectile that comes out when you kill them.
I'm in deep shit here.
Come on, give me a heart.
What is that?
I have no idea what that was.
I got killed by a fly that was orbiting me.
Huh?
I've never seen that.
How weird is that?
Okay, we're gonna gamble again or not gamble.
We're gonna vote.
Another vote is coming up.
Can I not just repeat the freaking vote I had last time or something?
Maybe not.
Okay, question mark.
I'm just gonna go random heart, random greed, and challenge.
I misspelled it, but that's okay.
Let's check.
I think it was a good run I was on there.
The thing is, though, Judas is so freaking fragile.
Like, you start with so little HP, it's horrible.
And I feel like every time I play Judas, I never find HP.
It's almost like the deck is stacked against me when I play Judas.
Maybe it's hard-coded into the game that when you play this character, chances of finding HP up items are just lower, you know?
Because I never get to find HP.
Okay, random heart and challenge is very close.
Still have 30 seconds left.
Ish.
Okay, looks like a random heart.
Yeah, let's do it.
Okay, oh, let me...
Yeah, 50% of the votes and challenge was 46%.
Very close.
Okay, here we go.
What's it gonna be?
Cane!
What was his deal?
Let me see, four damage.
That's pretty good.
And decent speed as well.
I mean, two hearts?
I mean, this is pretty good.
Maybe we'll do some stepping this time, depending on what we find.
Oh, man.
You want to come down here?
How am I gonna deal with you?
They're shooting way too fast.
Come on.
Sick.
Got a healing there.
I think if Judas had two hearts to start with instead of one, that character would go from, in my opinion, pretty bad to amazing.
That's how big a difference one heart makes in the game.
I don't even want this.
I guess it charms enemies.
Hey, you like this?
You're my friend now.
Act like it.
Oh, wait, I can keep farting.
But he still shoots at me, so I don't know.
Money room?
Cream catcher.
And pill.
Oh, wait a minute.
He just killed his friends.
Maybe the fart machine is not bad after all.
You see that?
That was amazing.
Kill him.
Oh, he's not actually damaging him.
All right.
Well, still good though.
Am I gonna?
No, no, no.
Let's not risk that.
Or should I?
Here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna blow this up in case there's a secret here.
There was not.
Now, this side?
Sure.
Oh, nice.
Not bad.
Yeah, get away from me.
Dude, the fart machine is one of my favorite items now.
Legitimately good.
Like, if you get back into a corner, you fart.
And then everything is right with the world again.
Nice.
Another money.
I could go look for some secrets.
And when I say some, I mean one.
Definitely here.
What?
Where else could it be?
Shit.
Okay, very nice.
Okay, I predict maybe here.
But let me check the other rooms.
Just to see what it looks like.
Okay, yeah, that definitely looks like something, doesn't it?
Fuck yeah!
And we're rich!
We have enough for the shop.
We can get the Dreamcatcher.
But do I really want it?
It's not that good, is it?
I mean, it's okay, but I could also get one blue, one bomb, which I need.
One pill and one key.
Oh wait, that's 15.
Okay, I can't get the key, but we have two keys already.
I'm gonna get... Oh wait, this is speed up!
Then I definitely want to buy it.
And then I'll take this one and that one.
Yeah, fuck the Dreamcatcher.
I mean, Dreamcatcher is okay, you know, but it's not like amazing.
Let's go.
Gimme me!
Boink!
What?
Dude, the fart machine!
Best item in the game!
Holy shit!
That's wild!
How good that is.
Oh ho!
Okay, well, I'm a believer.
I'm a believer now.
Will it finally dethrone the converter?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Boink!
Dude, it recharges mid-combat as well!
This item is broken.
Gimme.
We're gonna find five coins.
Sikes.
It's actually the best item.
It makes you so safe!
Tears up!
I'm so lucky!
It's the best run ever.
Now we just got to find some HP up.
Replaces tears with a charge shot that increases in size and damage.
Oh,
we can also... I wonder how much damage that is, if I just spam it.
Oh, look at this.
Okay, that was a boring, tinted rock.
Dude, are you serious?
I have the best items.
I can't lose!
Ha!
Count of a penny!
Chance to gain an I command now to leave me alone!
Nice.
Okay, I'm not happy about losing that half blue heart, though.
Eraser?
Yeah.
Wooden nickel?
Nah, definitely not replacing my active.
I think I'm an active enjoyer right now.
I don't know if it's better to just spam it or use this charged attack.
That's probably... both are pretty good.
It's incredible.
We have the boss here.
We can donate some blood, actually.
We do have a heart.
Become more rich.
Oh!
Audible blood bank!
Maybe.
Let me remind myself.
Deals half a heart of self-damage respond one to three coins.
Yeah.
Nah, I think I'm okay.
We're gonna get that heart up here.
Was there a heart in here as well?
There actually is.
We could get some coins.
Some more coins.
I think we should do it.
It's only three coins to buy, so.
And there's
a red I feel like that's unlucky when it says one to three.
Okay, now I'm good.
Actually, there's still a room to explore.
We're gonna go fart in their faces.
And they're gonna love it.
Sick.
Okay, wait.
Oh, okay.
Hold on a minute.
Something's off here.
Why did the door open last time?
I made a bomb on the blue fire.
So I thought maybe that was it, right?
But then I thought, okay, maybe the bomb also affected the door and that was it?
Wait, I don't know.
We're back to nothing right now on this.
Yeah, this is wrong.
Shit.
Oh, well.
Get your own nerd!
You're not gonna do anything?
You're not gonna eat yourself or something?
Oh, I split him in half.
Now I can charm him.
Yeah, look!
Split him in half and charm him.
Come on.
Oh, yo, yo.
Okay, though.
Pentagram!
We like that.
I am not gonna take the devil.
I'm going for angel.
That's right.
I'm a good boy.
I'm a righteous boy.
I don't, you know, make deals with devils.
Best level.
Okay, this is open.
We're doing it, then.
Okay, diagonals.
Go blow him up!
Haha!
No, no, no.
Oh, god.
Dude, this fart machine is so fun to use.
I'm not even kidding.
This may be my favorite item so far.
Lock up!
This is amazing.
More pills?
Oh, okay.
Oh, my god!
How my soul?
I guess I have two luck.
Uh, wait a minute.
I'm gonna get two fires with one here.
Okay.
Well, that's unexpected.
No blue hearts for me, though.
What the hell is this?
I'm gonna charm him.
I should have done that before when they were three of them.
I wonder if I can get a key from this guy.
This is the same guy you get when you, uh, when you step.
Actually, is it better to just spam?
I think it is, actually.
Dude, I've just stopped questioning what's happening in this run.
Everything is going amazingly.
I think I'm using up all the luck that I'm gonna have today with this guy.
Oh, look!
It is a piece of the key!
We got a step now.
I mean, assuming that we've... Wait, we're in I wonder if this secret room was gonna be like this if I found it the normal way as well.
Because that is very unusual for a secret room.
Whoa!
Wait, what am I doing?
Charm him!
Nice!
Mr. Me!
No, I'm getting, uh, this one.
And that's it, I think.
For now, at least.
I can't, I can't disregard this.
This is, it's too good.
The fart is immaculate.
Oh-ho!
Hit and run.
Nice.
Uh, right, go this way.
Oh, shit.
No problem.
That's the boss.
You know what?
Why not?
Let's go for it.
It's Peep.
Check this out, friend.
Oh, wait.
I should only charm when there's other enemies.
Otherwise, it's kind of useless.
Nice.
Dealing good damage.
Oh, wait!
I do take damage from creep!
I thought in these caves, I didn't, because the water.
I was mistaken.
Torn photo, nice.
More damage.
I'm getting so much damage here.
Can't be mad about that.
I just realized, me killing that angel.
Did I just mess up my chances at getting the angel room?
Because I don't think they're gonna enjoy me killing them.
But, oh, by the way, the fact that the angels have a key piece.
What did I wrote?
Uh, right?
Oh, no, I deleted it.
Bring in the photo.
No, always head in the clouds.
I think we gotta find a door in the clouds.
Meaning, uh, you know, up in heaven.
Nice.
Would love to find one more HP up.
Just one.
Oh my god, come on, please.
Wait, did I see a tinted rock?
No.
That one we did already.
Losing all my HP here.
And the charge shot is actually amazing against these guys.
Okay, going pretty well.
25 coins as well, I need to find a shop.
No way, I don't have a key?
Shit.
Wait, huh?
Ah, ah, here we go, here we go.
Massive.
What's it gonna be?
Rosary.
Three soul hearts, adds copies of the Bible to all item pools, and we get tears.
That is fantastic.
I'm so religious, but also not.
Uh, oh yeah, we had this.
Haha, sick.
Dude, getting all the good pills here.
Now I really shouldn't take any more pills.
Also, uh, where's the other secret room?
I feel like I should have seen it.
I could take Mr. Me if I wanted to, but then I'm gonna lose my fart.
No, I'm gonna keep my fart.
Like, shouldn't this reveal or?
Huh, maybe not.
Uh, let's actually go to the, uh, what's it called?
Curse.
Oh my god, totally worth.
Okay, and now we're leaving.
See you later nerds!
28 coins.
We gotta find a shop ASAP before we start not getting shops anymore, right?
More flooded caves.
Oh man, he almost hit me with that.
The artillery.
Double heart.
Oi, mistakes.
Uh, I'm gonna do this.
Good enough, I think.
Beautiful.
Exactly as calculated.
Arcade.
I mean, I could do that.
I have a lot of money.
I could also donate some HP here.
Child's heart.
Hey, that's nice.
I think I'd rather have that.
Thanks.
Let me go and grab some more hearts.
Oh wait, I could have gone down to zero red hearts.
It's just in my mind when I think zero red hearts.
It's like, uh, oh, I'm gonna die, right?
But that's not the case when you have blue hearts.
Okay, that should be it, I think.
Moving on.
Maybe we'll do some more gambling in a little bit here.
Battery.
Shit.
Really like charging up my shot.
It feels like I'm playing Azazel a little bit.
Tech X replaces tears with charged laser rings.
Damage in size of the rings.
Dude.
Yeah.
Fuck yeah.
That is awesome looking.
Oh wait, it's not doing that much damage.
I mean, I made a mistake.
Unless, unless I can.
Ah, but I can't, I can't spam it anymore.
The spam is gone.
Oh no, I made a mistake here.
Restock.
Wait, what?
Did I already get that?
Oh, that was last run.
Okay.
Messing with my mind.
Box of friends.
I wonder if this piece of key that I'm carrying right now is counting as a familiar.
Let me see if it says so.
Increased angel.
Oh, really?
Two and a half percent chance to convert red hearts into its...
Oh!
When assembled, unlocks a special door.
Oh yeah, 72% angel chance.
We gotta keep it.
Yeah, definitely.
But this is good to buy, for sure.
And I think I'll take this one too.
Actually should have bought that first, now that I think about it.
But it's okay.
We have found a treasure room and yeah, let's just go in here.
I think I actually degraded my attack with that pickup, unfortunately.
Okay, you know what?
Maybe not.
That was... Yep.
All right, that's pretty good.
I take it back.
That's pretty damn good.
And look at this, we get angels.
What if I blow them up?
Following familiar, the fire's slow.
Yeah, I'll take it.
Trisaclon has appeared.
Dude, let's try and blow them up.
Ahoy!
One of them has a blue shirt and the other one has a red shirt.
I don't know what that means.
You're now my friend.
Peekies!
Key piece one.
Dadski has appeared in the basement!
You unlock challenge 19.
Family man?
Filigree feather?
Wait a sec.
Wait, whoa, wait, wait.
Did it say I got Dadski or was it appeared in the basement?
Key piece one, key piece two.
Yeah, like it's full.
It's a familiar now.
Huh.
Okay.
But I'm not done exploring.
We're gonna go back.
Dude, it's going pretty well.
And you know what?
It's all thanks to the fart machine.
Single target, it's not that good, actually.
Should I go gamble?
Maybe.
Let's look for secrets.
Got five bombs?
No?
Ah, that was bad.
Maybe here.
Here.
Dammit.
Here!
I love the fort so much.
Wait, can I fart these on the other side?
No.
Can I actually affect items?
Okay.
Would be a cool way to do that.
Well, I think we're done here.
Two bombs left.
I will save them.
And again, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This looks promising right here.
One more try.
Fuck yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Oh, wait, there's two buttons.
Do it, Butorna.
Gold!
Actually, oh, wow.
Wow.
Okay.
I'm gonna blow this guy.
No, I'm gonna save my bomb.
Yeah.
Actually, hold on.
Are we gonna go full gamble?
What if the last one is over here?
Right here.
Damn.
Okay.
I deserve that.
Would love to get to that chest.
You know what?
Buy that bomb.
Holy shit.
Hey.
Okay.
That's too expensive.
That's my limit.
Can't do that.
Let's go.
Okay.
Next up is mom, but not now, but next one.
The dank depths.
It's gonna be dark in here.
Except it's not really dark.
I wonder if that's because we have a little angel with us.
I'm not gonna open that.
Kill him for me.
Dude, will you die?
What?
That guy has so much HP.
Look for tinted rocks.
These rocks are different looking, by the way.
These are special rocks.
Oh wait, you wanna... Let's be careful here.
You want coins?
Okay, I'll give you some coins.
We have two luck.
Should be good, right?
Oh, you're gonna give me battery.
I don't like that.
Jim.
Yeah.
How?
Wait, what the hell?
Okay, that was embarrassing.
This is not... It's not going too well, I gotta be honest.
Like, we haven't found any HP.
This is shaping up to be horrible now.
Wait!
We gotta... Wait a minute!
Is this it?
Uh.
Wait.
Fuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuck!
That door is open now, but for real.
And now we have a key.
While wait, if the door's open, I guess we don't need a key.
It's probably a different door, then.
There's more doors.
I'm so close to dying here.
This run is so cool.
I don't want to end it like this.
Please, no.
Okay, thank god.
What's that?
Best butt.
Want to fly familiar with the current room?
Sure.
Why not?
It's not that great.
Okay, please get me a blue heart.
Fasters!
This is the best run of all time!
The only problem is, we got to find some soul hearts now.
Plus one luck.
Oh, wait a sec.
Wait a sec.
It didn't increase the price of this one, though.
Oh, potato peeler.
Oh, man.
Wait, we're gonna come back for this?
For now, I need this to survive.
As soon as we find, like, a black or blue heart, you know what we're doing.
Jesus.
Wow.
Okay, I'm definitely getting in there, though.
That healing is immaculate.
Wow.
Wait, why is there a little rascal on the minimap?
Why is he highlighted like that?
Wait a minute.
Is he a special rascal?
Why is this guy highlighted?
Not that guy.
Take my money.
I don't... fuck you.
That's right.
Get out of my face.
All right.
Well, we still have rooms this way.
We got to find some blue hearts here.
Oh, this could be it.
Scary.
Okay.
Fight room is closed.
Oh, I can't stand on that.
Yeah.
But wait, we're not gonna take it yet.
Um, wait, what am I gonna do?
I'm gonna... I could go in there and do some HP.
That's gonna take half.
Oh, maybe it's a full HP.
I'm not sure.
I can't trust.
I don't trust like that.
I really don't.
And I can't get in here.
I have no bombs.
I'll be back.
They're gonna bomb me.
Yeah, there we go.
Look at that.
It's beautiful.
Absolutely amazing.
So that means we can actually open this now.
Is it worth it to pick up that heart?
I think it is.
We're gonna take it and go to the boss.
Wait, we have a bomb now.
We could do this.
Get in here.
Ah!
Fuck you!
Horrible.
Man, I wasted that heart now.
It's okay.
Stiff up a lip.
Um, oh man, I want to use my converter, but I also want to use my frickin' fort.
This guy better drop a blue one for me.
That's right, you ain't nothing!
Speed and damage.
I am not even gonna look at the devils.
No, not doing it.
Uh, I have to go back and grab the converter.
I gotta do it.
Then again, the fort is immaculate.
I could also gamble on a... Guys, this could be a health up.
If this is a health up...
Okay, that's pretty good as well.
It could also be a health down, I guess.
Uh, okay, that's... Dude, what is with these pills?
They're all fucking amazing.
Is there really no blue?
Uh, wait, I saw some blue flames.
Maybe we can, uh, destroy one more somewhere.
Yeah, here.
Man!
Okay, there's gotta be one more blue flame.
Or we can look for a actually, wait, wait, a secret could be over here.
See how this room is surrounding every other room here?
Or do I go for the flame?
Let's check every side first.
Oh, if we do it here, we can get the flame as well.
Okay, we didn't hit the flame, but that's okay.
It happens.
Some money.
I used all my bombs now.
That's not fantastic.
I kind of just want to convert.
But I also want to fart.
No, you know what?
Call me crazy, but I believe in the fart.
This may actually be better than the converter.
It sounds insane.
I'm not kidding.
This thing is so incredibly good.
We lost Angel just now.
Why?
Why did we lose Angel?
Now we gained Angel.
Yeah, I don't understand.
What are these weird rooms?
Okay, that's big.
We need that later.
Oh, Jesus.
No way.
Good thing I saved it, huh?
Nice.
Oh, that's so big.
Can I get use my key on it?
Come on, use the key.
You open the door.
I don't have any bombs.
Uh, go.
I was a little naughty there.
Oh, maybe should have waited picking that up.
Actually, I made a mistake.
That was not smart.
We should have waited.
They're jumping.
Okay.
Gotta be careful with those pills.
What?
Wait, what drops one?
Oh, that's the one that replicates the last pill I had, I guess.
We can use this actually to blow things up.
This is not bad.
Check this out.
Yo.
Okay, I thought for sure that would work.
Really?
We need to blow it up even more.
Okay, this way.
Nice.
What the hell is that?
Bible-tracked.
More chance of finding eternal hearts.
But maybe I don't want that.
This one is pretty good.
How come I can't scroll down anymore?
Oh, I guess I can't scroll on that one.
Increasingly finding red hearts.
Add an additional red heart to chests, tinted rocks, and destroyed machines.
Okay, you know what?
Maybe that will reduce the chance of finding black hearts.
Because if a black heart was supposed to spawn, maybe that item makes it more likely to remove the black heart and give me a red heart.
So I'm actually taking this.
I can see how the math could work like that, you know?
Okay.
Yeah, this fart machine is so worth it to keep.
Love hallways like this when I have this attack.
Oh my god!
I lost my eternal heart.
But at least we're rich, huh?
But what am I gonna spend the money on?
I'm not ready yet.
Honestly, kind of heavy.
I didn't find any soul hearts yet.
Otherwise, I would have regretted not taking this converter.
But of course, I'm also sad about it.
My fart missed everything.
Insane damage, less range, less tears.
Oof.
I mean, that's good for me.
Ah, but wait.
Then I charge slower, right?
Replaces tears with large, arcing bloodshots that burst into a spray of smaller bloodshots on impact.
The large shot deals increased damage but have a reduced fire rate.
Okay, I think it works pretty well with my charge.
Oh, it's really slow.
Oh, wait, what?
That's not what I expected at all.
Maybe that's good.
Enjoy, suckers!
Holy shit!
Okay, this is amazing.
This is amazing.
Wow.
Here, take some... Oh, this guy's gonna give me battery, right?
Yeah, okay.
We have a bunch of hearts scattered everywhere, so we're gonna donate a bunch.
I'll be back.
And we have a half heart here.
And a cart.
Oh, oh well.
It's okay.
This may not be worth it.
I don't know.
Oh, it's totally worth it.
I spoke too soon.
That was incredible.
It is always worth it.
You know what?
Let's get in here.
Oh, that's incredible.
Oh, I wish I had converter now.
Shit.
It's okay.
I'll be taking that.
And this one.
And then we're gonna go in here and try to blow this up.
Wonderful.
Uh-oh.
Okay, okay, it's a little awkward because you can't really shoot nearby.
You can only shoot, like, pretty far with it.
What?
Oh, it was one of those.
Can I?
Oh.
What happened?
Let me blow that up.
Tears up.
Wait.
Oh my god, it was hidden beneath the blanket?
Or, uh, rug.
Not blanket.
The one that tied the room together.
Uh, jumper cables?
Coupon?
Oh, wait.
Coupon.
Oh, no, I gotta donate a heart for this.
I can't do it, Captain.
Um, wait.
All future card drops are replaced with... Ooh.
I mean, pills have been pretty good for me.
I'm even more rich now.
Why isn't this a proper shop where I can spend money?
Like, uh, 4.5 volt.
What is this?
Dealing damage to enemies.
Gradually recharges active items.
No, I don't need that.
Makes one item in the shop or devil room free.
Select it at random.
So this should make one of these free, right?
I don't... This is like a gamble if I do this.
I'm doing it!
Sick.
Pill for me.
Teleport to a random room, though.
I don't know if I like that, though.
Wait, what is the random room right now?
Can I not pick this up?
Okay.
Let's try it.
Telepills.
Okay, well, every room is cleared.
So, whatever.
Where was I just now?
Oh, yeah, I was in this room.
Let's go back there.
There was more stuff I wanted to do.
Also, it's so fitting that there was pills in the opens all... Oh!
What the fuck?
I didn't even see that.
So that means if I walk around now, I should be able to find a secret room.
Unless I had to be in the room where the secret room is when I activate the item.
I don't think so.
Okay, I need to blow something up here.
Let's blow these guys up.
Oh, that's actually pretty cool.
That's a nice one.
We're gonna get rich from that, but we already are rich, so I don't know.
Oh, that's too risky grabbing that coin.
I didn't mean to jump down!
God damn it!
Ah, I hate myself.
I really do.
Jesus Christ.
We're gonna pre-charge.
This is insane!
The problem is, though, I can't see projectiles when I do this.
So I need to simply... uh, wait, wait.
Range?
Oh, nice.
Actually, maybe range is bad for me.
Nah, we're just gonna keep going.
Oh, wait, am I hitting the... Oh, yeah, am I raging?
Oh, no.
Maybe if I go in a corner and do this.
Oh, technique discovered!
This is how we do it, baby.
That's how we do it.
Insane.
Pre-charge.
Like, I'm blind when I do it.
I'm just gonna hope for the best.
Oh, man, what a combo.
What a combo.
This is what I mean, like, how cool... Wait, why is there blood on that chest?
Wait a minute.
Are spikes gonna come out of that one?
I'm not gonna open it.
I said spikes.
Enjoy.
Oh, these assholes are actually annoying.
Do you mind dying?
Perhaps?
Open up!
Jesus.
Drops.
Okay.
I mean, I can do that here.
Amazing.
Telescope lens.
Increases the chance of a planetarium spawning.
Dude, whatever this planetarium is, it better be the most amazing thing that has ever existed in this game.
I've never seen one, and every item you get that has anything to do with it, increases the chance by, like, five to ten percent.
Planetariums can spawn in the womb and corpse.
Say what?
Corpse?
I don't like that.
Watch this.
Smart!
Wish I had the converter.
No, I walked into the laser.
I just lost the heart I got.
It's real sad.
Oh, fuck.
I don't have a key.
Well, that's not good.
Ah, well.
Poish.
Out of the corner!
I'm glad I can't pick up more horse.
That means I'm at least full on red hearts.
Dude, this is great.
Guys, this is fantastic.
Wow.
Dude, why is every tear or pill amazing?
Have I even... Okay, I guess I've gotten the diarrhea, but besides that, it's like amazing pills.
I will never attain this level of luck again.
Oh, it's these guys.
Okay, watch this.
We're gonna...
Enjoy!
Wake up.
I think I got hit, actually, so we need to go grab some hearts.
Something hit me before.
I felt a disturbance in the forces now, but in the past.
No?
Okay.
I was wrong.
We could actually go step.
I think we have two red hearts.
Oh, wait.
That's not a step room.
We cannot go in there.
We're gonna lose a full HP upon entering.
Remember.
Because we're in the womb.
Here we go.
Wish me luck.
Teratoma.
Yep.
That will do it.
Magic eight ball increases the chance of planetariums.
Okay, we got a fine one this time, huh?
With all these... Oh.
Yeah!
Nice!
And this one is a coin and then we have... hmm.
I can't do it.
I don't have HP.
We gotta keep going down here.
So, wait a minute.
Hold on.
Now that I have such a big chance of finding planetariums.
Maybe I should go look for secret rooms here.
There.
Not there.
Let me keep an eye out here.
Maybe here.
I didn't mean to do that just now.
That was a mistake.
Okay, last try is gonna be maybe here.
But that's only one bomb.
Oh, no.
It's not there.
Hmm.
I think we're leaving.
Yeah, I'm done.
I love how ridiculous I look with these VR goggles on.
It's kind of cool.
I like the look.
I mean, we can peek inside.
Be still.
We can't do it.
But what we can't do is not go back.
Why is that gotta appear when I can't take it, you know?
It's... but it's okay.
Like, I already have a pretty fucking sick combo going here.
We don't need more.
Like, oh my god, I do so much damage.
It's actually absurd.
What I need right now is survival.
Pure, pure survival.
Or just kill them before they can do anything.
Oh, I thought enemies were in here.
Oh, yeah, baby.
I mean, I'm too rich now.
Keep moving, keep moving, keep moving.
Dude, stop with the money!
Why are there so many money?
I don't get it.
Well, I know what I'm spending my money on.
I'm scared of just staying near the machine, though, in case something blows up.
So I'm gonna...
Yeah, see?
We're gonna do that.
It's gonna take a million years, but let's bounce between them.
We need more speed.
Oh, I need you to grant me blue hearts.
Black hearts.
No more money.
Actually, red hearts are good, too.
I can donate to this guy in the center and then grab red hearts from the machines.
He says he takes half a red heart, but I don't believe him.
I think he's gonna take a full one.
Oh, no, absolutely not that one.
Let me try.
Yeah, look, he took a full one, that bastard.
That's one machine down.
Okay.
At least I get to spend my money.
Would also like to donate the money to the shop.
Oh, okay, that's actually nice.
And we can go down here and we can go crazy.
This is so much nicer.
Speed.
Unident.
Do I risk it?
Oh my god, what a god!
What is that?
Wait, do I have something that makes all pills good or something?
I don't understand.
Uh, no.
Oh, wait a minute.
All future... Isaac can hold two pills at once, sponsored, random, all future card drops.
No, that, okay.
I don't know what's happening.
I gotta be honest, I don't know what's going on right now.
Experiment.
The pills are good.
Yeah, give me a copy of the last pill.
Okay, it says random stat down, random stat up.
It's only up!
Pills are good.
How about a health up pill?
Can we have that?
I don't want explosive diarrhea.
That's very not good for me right now.
The kidney bean.
Uh, yeah, give me this.
We can donate to this guy now.
We're not gonna speak of this.
We're gonna do a poll now?
What's happening next?
We will never speak of this again.
Here, let me, let me bring up the neutralizer.
Look into this light, okay?
Look, look into this light.
Wait, wait.
No, oh my god.
That's so bad.
That's probably the worst thing I've ever done.
That right there tops it all.
Here, poll is up.
One minute.
I cannot believe that.
I can't believe I just, like this run was so fucking fun.
And I ruined it.
I did, I ruined it all.
Hold on, I'm gonna open chat.
Guys, what do you think of that?
What do you think of that one?
Was that, I mean, that was not even intentional rage bait.
That was legitimately just me completely messing it up.
I fucked it up, guys.
I did.
We need speed run.
We can do a speed run, I guess.
But I, okay, we can do a speed run.
A random speed run.
How about that?
I like that.
But what actually won the poll?
Okay, random hard won the poll.
So we're gonna do a random speed run then.
That sounds good.
Why not?
We're gonna combine two things here.
Here we go.
Let's do this.
Look, don't look at the win streak.
It doesn't matter.
Magdalene.
Okay.
Oh, she's slow though.
How are we gonna run fast when she's so slow?
Okay, there we go.
Nice.
Very nice.
Dude, I can't believe I found this item already.
Are you kidding me?
This is the most insane thing of all time.
The door opened right in front of me!
Holy shit!
Nah, come on, guys.
I knew I, I knew I fucked it up with the thing.
Come on.
It was, it was, it was a troll.
I didn't plan on doing it, but I realized all of the soon as I got in, and I was like, okay, let me fuck with you guys for a bit.
The wiz.
Isaac fires two tiers at once, but a split diagonal egg.
I didn't find any item, by the way.
I was just kidding.
Why did I pick that up?
I don't like this effect.
I guess they're spectral.
I guess if you shoot two bullets, you go twice as fast.
Oh, oh, look at this.
There's a rock here, but we got to go fast.
I also got to heal.
I got to reorient my angles here.
Oh, god.
Jesus.
Whoa!
Okay, then.
Calm down.
Yeah, the split is messing with me.
Oh, no.
Oh, I'm going to die.
Wait, no, I don't.
I have so much HP.
What?
One of them died.
We're actually okay.
We're okay.
Dude, there's the hardest balls of all time.
Apparently.
Give me something that gives me speed or that.
That's cool too.
We're going.
Speed.
Ultimate speed.
And we got to remember to use the active so we can heal up.
Okay,
now it's your turn, buddy.
Sick.
Dude, we could actually go step with this character, but we don't have time for that.
We're speed running.
Good.
What the hell is that?
Mucomycosis?
Spore shot?
A chance to fire fungus shots that stick to enemies.
When attached, fungus shots grow to a certain size and explode into a damaging poison gas cloud that also fires additional homing fungus shots.
Wow.
So it is actually like a disease that spreads through the population.
I like it.
We got to go faster.
It's going to explode.
Oh, wait, what?
Why didn't I?
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
Too bad that if you killed them when they have it on, it gets wasted.
Oh, shit.
Wait, we don't have time for that.
We got to go.
Oh, okay.
Right.
It's the same thing I had last run.
Dude, the split shot sucks.
Oh, man.
Jumped over the fence.
Come here.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, this is nice, actually.
Let the disease spread through the population.
Hahaha.
Sick.
Speed.
Gurgling.
This one is going to be tough.
This is going to be really tough.
Unless we get the disease going, that's what we need here.
It's going.
Okay, it's pretty good.
We're chilling.
That's amazing.
Uh, move on.
We're definitely taking devil deals.
As this character, you better believe it.
Best area.
Okay.
Uh, oh, wait.
If I do this here, it's going to open up and we're going to be cool.
Beautiful.
Just beautiful.
This is so awkward.
Explode.
Yeah, you're, you're, you're deceased.
Good.
Spread the disease.
That's right.
Yeah, not bad.
We got an early disease going.
I love the disease.
Terrento.
I will grab that.
Oh, it's this stuff again.
What the hell?
Okay, it's not that scary, though.
It was last time.
That's fine.
A heart dropped.
Oh, you're not even dead.
Dude, we can totally step.
If we get the opportunity,
this guy is on some kind of drug.
He's never been this crazy before.
That's a new one.
Uh, he was all, wow.
Wow.
Dude, stepping.
No, speed.
Full speed.
We are officially ahead of the timer.
Go, go, go, go, go.
How did I dodge that?
I'll tell you how.
Skill.
Um, the best to ever do it.
Okay, this is going to be annoying, though.
It's going to be one of those, huh?
Looks like the disease does not fall them into the floor.
This brings me sadness.
So tanky.
How?
Like, die, man.
This guy can't die.
He's more tanky than a boss.
Insanity.
I accidentally used my active.
That's okay.
That's actually huge.
Spread the disease to as many as possible and move on.
No, boss.
We can step here.
Come here.
He's dead.
Ex-lax.
I'm stepping.
I know we're on a timer, but I'm going to step.
You don't get this opportunity every day.
Sick.
Wow.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
All right, no problem.
Okay, here we go.
Yeah, get deceased, nerd.
Oh, man.
My diagonal is not going to vibe well with his diagonal.
Oh, God.
How?
Even angels can't resist my diseases here.
Angelic prism.
All right.
Money.
We're wasting a lot of time here, though.
We really got to move on, I think.
Maybe just a little bit more.
No, we're done.
No, we're not done.
Fuck.
Okay, here we go.
We're going to get the key if we don't fuck it up.
This guy has different attacks.
I feel like he's easier.
That's right.
Get blown up, son.
I'm in a hurry here, okay?
We got to end this fast.
I ain't got time for your shit.
What's this?
What's happening?
What the fuck is this?
We opened the door.
No.
Wow.
Okay, so that's how you do it.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
Hold on a minute.
What even is this place?
A chance to fire void tears that summon Bighorn's hand?
This one is really good.
Wandering Harbinger.
Shifts form.
It's not that fantastic.
I would say this one, dude.
This one is... I mean, we could do multiple.
We have so many hearts.
Oh my god.
Fuck this one.
Maybe we dig?
No.
I can't take another active.
I like this active.
Seven seals.
Um.
Nah.
We're gonna, we're gonna go in here.
Mega Satan.
Oh shit.
Oh.
What the fuck is this?
Oh my god.
Yeah, you're about to die, motherfucker.
You can't stand my diseases.
I know you can't.
Am I even hitting anything?
Oh, oh, okay.
You got little guys?
I see.
I see how it is.
No problem.
Everyone's getting deceased here.
Wow.
Okay, that's weird.
This guy's got lasers.
How come this guy's not dying, though?
I can't even see his HP bar.
Oh, he's hiding.
How come this guy can't die?
I've done so much damage to him.
I'm gonna blow you up.
Okay, didn't do nothing.
Okay, he finally died.
Oh shit.
Oh, I think I'm dead here.
I have no HP.
Okay, Mega Satan.
Do we have a Mega Isaac?
God damn it.
What the hell?
Okay, man.
Stepping is the new shit.
I love to step.
Okay, let's do a challenge now.
I will veto the poll and say challenge time.
We're gonna switch it up.
That was kind of crazy what just happened.
I'm excited.
I'm scared.
But I'm also, you know, ready to move on here.
I need to process what just occurred.
Like, that was insane.
So you step on the thing, you get key, then you get another key, then it combine, and then you keep stepping until you get teleported to the area that opens the door.
I got you, man.
I got you.
Oh, we also have it tinted here.
We're gonna finally do this challenge now, by the way.
There's no way we're gonna mess it up again.
I've been so close, tasting that victory so many times.
Never again.
Pay to play.
I don't think I want that.
I don't really want anything here.
I mean, unless we get a lot of coins this run.
Depends.
Let's go around and see.
How dare you go incognito on me.
I just can't hit him.
My aim is so bad.
Oh yeah, okay, that's pretty good.
Oh, die shard.
It's a shard of the d6?
I see now.
And what about this one?
Whatever.
Oh wait, it revealed a... Ah, it revealed secret rooms.
Not bad.
So on this character, we want to be on low HP, actually.
Oh no, I don't have any bombs.
Tell me we find some bombs.
Really?
Could I buy a bomb?
Oh my god, that's crazy.
Two secret rooms right there, and I can't do anything about it.
That kills me.
I mean, the damage is good right now, even though we're not a whore.
Nice.
Health.
Oh, okay.
Moving on.
Why is she laughing at my PP anyway?
She secretly wants it.
Come on.
Come here.
Also, I'm still kind of in speed run mode, even though I didn't need to be.
This is a challenge now.
It's different.
I will say, though, like, just speed running, trying to go fast is really fun.
Like, just in itself, you know?
I just enjoy trying to go faster and faster.
Shit.
Man, I have no keys.
I got nothing.
I'm poor.
I'm poor and I'm a whore.
Okay, we got a key.
I'm ready for the treasure room now, please.
Oh yeah, let me use the knife here.
I mean, it's a little too risky because you gotta get up real next to them.
You gotta touch, you know, cheek to cheek.
These two rooms will take 10 years.
Massive.
Oh, I see that.
We can blow that up later.
If we find a bomb.
Okay.
I'm not excited about any of this.
I'm just not.
Yeah, rip.
He just got charmed.
And he got feared.
Hairpin.
Fully charges Isaac's active item when entering.
No, that's bullshit.
But I guess it's a... Oh, it's a trinket, okay.
Don't really want that.
Okay, make me rich.
I believe.
I said make me rich.
I can't believe I just did that.
I'm not feeling it though.
This is one of those where I just lose everything.
Hey!
Totally worth now.
Exactly what I've been needing.
And that's that.
Very huge.
We're gonna bomb this up here.
Not here, next one.
That one.
Nice!
You know what we're gonna do then?
Wait, 0.93 damage.
Wait, we gain damage every time we do that?
Oh, hold on.
I need to move this mouse pad out of the way.
It's really annoying me.
There we go.
Let's see here.
Damage is Isaac's granted damage up for the current... Oh, it's only the room.
Okay, I see.
Then I get it.
Okay, now we have good damage.
Let's use it.
We also have one bomb left in case we find something else.
Like a tinted rock.
Bot penny.
Yeah.
No.
Actually, I want to find a Bible.
That would be pretty sick.
Time for the boss.
It's the window.
All the damage is good.
It's really good.
Yeah, and there he goes.
I didn't mean to pick that up.
That was a mistake.
Good.
Uh, wait.
Mom, do your worst.
Okay.
So, what's this?
Two spooky?
Two shot speed?
Uh, that's good.
Taking that?
Absolutely.
The whole idea is to be low on red hearts anyway.
Oh man, I could really eat candy.
I haven't eaten candy in over a month, if you can believe that.
Just the thought of eating candy right now is making me really happy.
Doish.
Careful.
Okay, you know what?
This damage is not cutting it.
We're going down.
I guess I should have done it in here just to gain that a little bit extra.
It didn't even matter.
Man, the fear is so good.
We now have fear on shots and proximity.
Okay, I like that actually.
Oh, I forgot I had the die shard.
We gotta use that on something.
Yeah, get scared of me.
Oh, man.
Not bad.
Jackie!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Jumps right out on my keyboard.
That rascal.
It's not even feeding time yet.
I don't know what she's doing.
Scared the crap out of me too.
Oh, sack hit.
Sponsors sack.
I think I'll buy this.
Yep.
What is it, Jackie?
You're going to be fed soon, don't worry.
Feeding time is coming up.
Oh, that's a nice coincidence.
Oh, what the...
disco!
Wow!
What is happening here?
I didn't mean to pick that actually do this and then... there we go.
Matchbook.
Yeah.
Uh oh.
So what is this room here?
What's happening?
Can I open doors?
I have to try this.
No?
Okay.
What about you?
Why is this room so weird?
Okay.
Well, wait, wait, wait.
Treasure room.
Not that way.
Show me treasure room.
Jackie is playing with my feet.
She wants attention right now.
You can play with my feet.
That's fine.
But if you jump on the table, you're going to give me a heart attack.
Okay.
Not this way.
Why the hell is this treasure room?
This is a really good run so far, by the way.
This is the stuff of dreams right here.
What's happening here?
I... I literally have no idea.
Everything that happens is just so freaking random.
It's crazy.
Like, okay.
Blow up a blue flame.
Door opens.
Kill an enemy.
I kill an enemy.
Door does not open.
It's just... it's got to be completely random.
You clear a room and then it's just randomized whether or not that door opens.
You're lucky or you're not.
Sweet.
The treasure room is eluding me.
Wait, is there no treasure room on this floor?
Okay.
No treasure room on Flooded.
I don't know what else to think.
Like, who's in my damn mind here?
Jackie!
What is it?
Huh?
There's nothing.
I'm not hiding your food up here, you know?
Okay.
He's going crazy right now.
Imagine there's a killer in the other room.
And I'm just not listening.
Just like, uh, what is that dog, you know?
The scared dog in that TV show.
Wait, I should have done that in the boss room.
Fuck.
Whoops.
He jumps away from me.
Because he's scared, I guess.
He's a feared.
Keep him scared.
Whoa.
That was clean.
Absolutely clean.
We're getting range and minor contact damage.
That's okay, I guess.
No deals?
Hey, there's actually a timer here.
I thought for some reason I was like, oh, in challenge rooms or in challenge, um, runs.
There's no timer, you know, but there is.
So I'm actually gonna try and speed up a little bit here.
We have good... Jackie!
Come on!
Okay, hold on.
I gotta check what's going on.
What is it?
Okay, I don't know what... why is she so... attention seeking right now.
Usually she's exactly like that, right when I end the stream, you know?
It's actually almost clockwork.
I end the stream, then I stop talking, right?
And she knows, okay, now it's time to play.
So she comes in here, but she's not doing that now.
I don't understand why.
I wanted to go fast.
I can't hit him.
You know what?
Me just move as you just stand still and shoot.
That's a better chance of hitting something.
Arcade.
I don't have time for that.
No time.
We gotta go fast.
Ah, damn it.
What's that?
Teleport to treasure room.
There's a planetarium.
Okay, please let it be the freaking planetarium.
No, I'm starting to believe I'm being gaslighted by the game.
That room does not exist.
It is a lie.
Whisperings of the planetarium in the dark.
I'm actually, you know what?
I'm gonna save my razor blade for the boss room this time.
This is actually the best way to do it, I guess.
Like, I could use it now, but I'm not gonna.
Now, where are you?
Kill the little guy.
Okay, very clean.
I think boss up here.
Nah, it's a shop room.
Ah, man, this room is taking forever.
I don't think we're gonna be able to catch up.
Okay, we gotta do it.
It's too slow.
I wanted to save it, but nope.
Uh, let me get this.
Hey, pretty good.
Okay.
Four coins.
Secret revealed here.
Where?
Huh?
Wait, it's here.
I missed it.
Oh, there!
I see.
Uh, we can do this.
In fact, that's ideal.
Uh, blow them up.
Uh, we can take that.
Okay.
Where actually is this boss?
Another item.
Placebo, pill mimic.
Uh,
yeah.
Only makes sense when you have a pill.
I like the razor.
Our tears are too big.
Here we go.
I think we're hopelessly behind, though, unfortunately.
Oh,
okay.
Shot speed up.
What's that?
Wheel of, oh, Wheel of Fortune.
Sponsor slot.
Oh, it's the slot machine thing.
Actually, let's do that.
You were born wrong.
Hey, it blew hard.
Huge.
I like the world, but it's useless for me right now.
Because I want to keep the, the d6 thingy.
Actually, we can use the d6 in the devil room.
This is what we're gonna do.
Bring him the photo.
Why so blue?
Okay, let's go.
No!
No items.
Unless he drops an item.
I wouldn't mind that.
Yeah, be afraid of me.
I don't know what the item is gonna be, so it's useless.
My Christmas present.
Makes tears and increase in damage and size.
All right, well, so that means more range, the better.
Reveals.
Should I keep this?
I'm gonna keep this.
Re-roll a bit more here.
What the hell is that?
Is this range?
No, that's the weird one.
I could actually go for that.
What the hell is this?
Black tooth.
Poison two, double I6 damage.
Increasing with a lock, not worth it.
Devil angel.
Oh, dude, we could totally go for this.
Instead of the re-roll.
Yeah, go!
We don't have time.
I think we're too far behind anyway.
Yeah, the timer's gone!
Okay, yeah.
I'll be teleporting.
Okay, so what do we have?
A headless baby.
You know, it's a trail of damage and creep and oh.
Wait, I could take this and then use this.
Book of Belial.
I guess the razor is useless now.
Wait, why is that a question mark?
What?
I know what it is.
I've been carrying it around, hello.
I can't blow this guy up.
Find the boss.
Like, I have so many hearts right now.
I just need to get on with it and end, you know, before I lose them all to random rooms.
Oh, that's big.
Ah,
I'm not happy about this.
Oh, look at this one.
Five?
Consult the manual.
Restart current floor.
Okay, okay, okay.
But with what condition?
This is what we need to figure out.
I'll be back for this.
Let's clear the floor and do that.
See what happens then.
They're gonna jump.
Bad gas, that's for you.
I actually killed him with that.
Fear is really good against these guys because they turn around, you know.
Nice.
I actually can't get hit by them because if they get close, they get feared.
Bible!
Or actually range.
That is what I need.
The more range, the more my tiers are gonna damage.
Oh, I thought it was empty!
Bastards!
What was that delay though?
Oh, that's big.
Very nice.
Give me something good.
Ah, just kidding.
Blow it up.
You want keys?
You're gonna have some keys.
Oh, you bastard.
Not worth it.
Hate those guys.
Let's go!
Six, six, six.
Maximum damage.
Nice.
Speed.
Oh, more range.
Fantastic.
That means my shots are gonna get so big and deal so much damage.
Oh, right.
That was that room.
I'm just gonna move on.
It's going swimmingly.
This is the run where we actually get to do the challenge.
It hurts my soul when I lose something like that.
Just unnecessary damage taken, you know.
Oh, we can do two for one here.
A Hierophant.
That's good!
Those guys need to die fast before they start dealing massive damage.
Yes.
I'm gonna mess you up, son.
The damage is pretty good.
This way.
I will say though, this challenge has been difficult.
Just simply because I've lost to it so many times.
I don't know why it's actually so difficult, because it's just another run, it seems.
Like, there's nothing more difficult about this than a normal run.
What?
Yeah, get away from me.
Let me in.
Oh wait, I forgot about the dice room.
Shit.
That was last floor.
I just got reminded by the door.
Five coins.
Why not?
It says Chariot.
That's decent.
Dude, I'm super fast.
Am I really gonna have to...
Yeah, okay then.
This room sucks.
Man!
Okay.
Brom!
Be afraid, be afraid!
Still no boss.
This is so convenient.
Yeah, the poop worked against you there, huh?
I can just chill in a corner, actually.
Here we go!
Wait,
I have a theory.
I can just stand in the middle.
No enemy's gonna come close to me.
Because they're gonna get feared.
Well, they are gonna shoot, I guess.
Okay, I mean, this is going pretty well.
That extra speed really helps to dodge the mom attack.
I mean, this is going swimmingly.
Not bad, not bad at all.
Let's see what we get.
That's really nice.
Shot speed is not too consequential.
I like it.
Book of Sin, sponsored now.
Little horn.
Boy, actually, this is pretty good.
Three blue hearts, though.
I think it's worth it.
Getting a little bit of extra damage could help out.
That was a bit risky to grab that item, but I think it's okay.
We just gotta, you know, lock in now and not take too much unnecessary damage.
Ah, but we're lost.
That's not good.
That's really not good.
The eye?
Fuck.
No way, it hit me twice!
I'm angry now.
I'm not gonna take it anymore.
And I'm getting rich now, when there's no shops anymore.
The time of the shop has passed.
Yeah, that hand is adding so much DPS.
I think I did the right thing, taking that.
Oh, fuck no.
Nope.
Good luck with that.
I'm not gonna be a part of that.
Rough.
Oh man, this is actually just over already.
I can't believe we're gonna lose again!
I don't want to!
Oh, I really don't want to lose this again.
Okay, that's good.
Half a heart is something.
This guy wants red hearts.
I'm gonna blow them up.
I need to find a boss fast.
Come on.
I mean,
I don't know what it is with this challenge.
It's every time I hit the womb, man.
Everything just falls apart.
Every time.
At least we have a door opening somewhere.
That's exciting.
If we can find it.
Wow, you guys, a tank is hell!
But I guess you are kind of a boss in a weird way?
Nice.
There we go.
Look how angry he is.
Just like me.
No, I'd rather have this.
Chariot.
Here we go!
Mr. Fred!
That's a new one.
What is that?
That hit me?
Just how?
Was it creep or what?
I think it was creep.
We can still die here.
Uh, yeah, soul heart.
We love that.
Oh, really?
Dude, I can't afford this.
What is it?
Death?
No, absolutely not.
That's the worst thing ever.
I mean, it's not, but right now it is.
In this moment.
Okay, go.
All right, this is it.
Can we do it?
Oh, wait a minute.
This is not even it.
There's more after this.
Oh, shit.
We're not done after this.
We can't win.
Why did I trade away my red hearts?
Never should have done it.
My range, though, is out of control.
I should be playing Space Invaders, like 24-7.
Boy, yep.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Go!
Boss?
What's happening?
Okay, I'm just gonna activate.
Just get the damage in.
I don't trust like this at all.
Chest room.
Nice!
Oh, no.
Scary.
Oh, that was actually kind of nice.
Let's see where they are.
Okay, we can't see it yet.
How did that hit me, man?
That was fast as light!
Unbelievable.
This is gonna be a rough one.
Delial, help me.
These eyes are gonna kill me.
Maybe.
Kill it!
Oh, they're dead, they're dead, they're dead, they're dead.
Now just deal that damage.
Don't mess it up.
We got dudes.
I hate dudes.
Okay, you're back now.
Fuck!
Don't go that way!
We're in trouble, I think.
Not the laser!
This challenge is impossible!
Okay, ultimate speedrun now.
I'm gonna knock this challenge out of the park today.
I can't stand it anymore.
We are not taking any devil deals ever again in this challenge.
What I need is a converter.
Grant me the item that allows me to win the game, please.
I need to convert all those... I could have converted all those hearts that I had.
Okay, that's a good start.
Except we got... oh, okay.
It's not the jiggly ones, luckily.
I'll be taking that.
Speedrun, speedrun, speedrun.
Dingle time.
He's gonna damage me, I know it.
Oish.
I thought you were gonna charge me there.
Here he comes.
Oh, he was gonna charge me.
Then something happened.
Okay.
Okay, when I fear him, he stops his charge.
Oi, oi, oi.
Yeah, baby!
Okay, good stuff.
Good.
Okay, moving on.
That's an extra heart.
Incredible.
And we're ahead of the timer.
I just puked up a razor blade?
I think that's the first time I've seen that one.
Uh, why not?
Actually worth.
Good.
This guy's gonna throw a bomb when he dies.
Uh,
don't go in there.
No time.
Whoa.
Hey, that's huge.
You know what?
I'm gonna hurt myself in a moment here.
First, we gotta locate the boss, though.
Actually, no, do it here.
One more.
I have a bad feeling about this room.
Okay, that was a bit scary.
Nice.
Another blue heart.
Let's go.
Speed!
The window.
You bastard, man.
Wow, my damage is kind of really good.
Nice.
Let's see what we got here.
What is that?
Salt for Grant's brimstone for the current room, activating twice in the same room, Grant's more powerful.
No, thanks.
Nice.
I am taking no deals, like I said.
No deals.
I'm gonna get a converter and I'm gonna convert everything.
I need it.
Uh, Necromonicon.
Oh, wait a minute.
We also have a battery here.
Yeah?
Two flies?
Isn't that like the most horrible thing that could have happened?
Bro, oh wait, these are not normal flies.
Ah, these are the different ones.
Okay, let's see.
This poop was different.
Okay, I don't know what that does.
It's like the rainbow poop.
It's a mystery.
Speed, speed, speed, speed, speed.
Wow, that was close.
That opened now.
Okay, let's just go for it then.
Okay,
ultimate speed run strategies are being employed here.
Sick.
Go, go, go, go, go.
No.
My disappointment is immeasurable.
That's for you.
Nice.
Good.
Solid.
Yes, baby.
Yes.
Oh, and one of these as well.
That's incredible.
Wait, I wonder if that's going to consume...
Oh, don't tell me it's going to consume the one with the elemental on it.
Or the eternal.
If that actually happens, I'm going to be so sad.
Okay, thank God.
I think I may have tried this once before, but I don't remember.
Okay.
What did I just pick up anyway?
Oh yeah, right.
That's the last one.
I had the same one last time.
Yeah.
Gaining it back.
Wow!
Like, you got to be ready here for these types of rooms.
Fast, fast, fast.
Speed, speed, speed.
Get up, get up, get up, get up.
Come on, you bastard.
I don't have time for this.
All right, let's go this way.
No, down here.
I'm actually going to do this.
Good.
Nice.
Get him out of the equation.
That's good stuff.
Damage is really good now.
80% of drop hearts are replaced with keys.
No, thanks.
Then again, all heart drops become black hearts?
No.
Maybe.
Uh, huh.
That's actually kind of an interesting proposition.
I'm going to say no.
It was interesting.
It basically means 20% of all red hearts are going to become black hearts.
Which I guess could become really big in rooms where like a million red hearts spawn.
You know the ones.
But I wouldn't even have gotten these items if not for the poop trinket.
Nice.
Boss, show thyself.
What's that?
Teleport to the shop?
Oh, that's right here.
Save a key.
Oh, coupon!
Why not?
Piggy bank.
Yeah, I like it.
I buy everything.
I think I may keep this.
The era of self-damage has gone no more.
You just got to stay on low HP now.
Experimental Bill.
I'm just happy it's not laser.
Go, go, go, go, go.
That's for you.
Speed.
Yeah, M.T.
is good.
M.T.
All right, what do you got, son?
He destroyed the fires for me.
That's kind of cool.
Ah, come on now.
I feel like he always drops this item.
Wait, is this predetermined?
Because it's a challenge.
Maybe some of these things are predetermined here.
Like custom tailored for this challenge.
Like I got the fear just like last time.
I'm getting this just like last time.
You know?
God damn it, man.
Yikes.
It's getting a little bit dangerous here.
What's that?
Wow.
My flies helped me out there.
Oh, thanks.
Damage is really good.
Kill him fast before he kills me.
Oh man, I went the entirely wrong way here.
Everything's good as south, not north.
Really unfortunate.
Not that way either.
Is it going to be the last path I take?
That's crazy.
I think I'm still ahead of the timer though.
Like I've been going fast here.
This is really good.
If I get a devil deal, I can actually coupon it.
That's worth.
No, what is that sabotage?
Did you see that shit?
Jesus.
Wow.
Well, rib my damage.
Man, I cannot believe that just happened.
At least the spiders get feared when they come close to me.
Damage and...
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
Unfortunately, no deal either.
May as well take this at this point.
We got to find a blood donation machine.
And we're still ahead of the timer.
Oh, the dang depths.
Curse of something bad.
Come on then, guys.
Get out here.
Oh, actually.
Imagine a converter right now, dude.
It would pretty much guarantee the win.
I'm gonna destroy that.
And I hit both.
Except not nice.
Go, go, go, go, go.
I'm actually more scared of these guys than mom.
I will say though, my damage right now, even without being a whore is decent.
Like, my tears are good, you know.
It's kind of working.
Nah, I don't need that.
Here we go.
A specialized door is open.
This is the time we find it.
Anarchist cookbook.
Bible!
Wait, uh...
Oh, Jackie.
Jackie, what is it with you today, huh?
You cannot be sitting there.
You can sit over there in the corner, that's nice.
Okay, uh, so let me see here.
We're three out of three on...
Aha, that's it.
Okay, I see.
I see.
Uh, wait, should I...
Maybe I actually take the Bible.
But first, I'm gonna use this coupon on something good.
We're gonna get a devil deal, use the coupon, change it for the Bible, and go.
This is the plan.
And it's a great plan.
I couldn't see them, it was dark.
Uh, oh no, no, no, no, no.
Jimmy!
Okay.
That went better than expected.
Tomato!
Nice.
There's the boss.
Wait, how come we're not taking...
Jackie!
No!
Go, go over there in the corner of the table and sit.
Sit in the corner.
She is so intrigued by whatever I'm doing right here.
I think she's loving Isaac as much as I am.
There's another guy there.
Booster pack, hmm.
Ooh, a pillow.
Jackie, oh my god.
You can't, I don't know what the hell is going on with Jackie right now.
Like, she just needs to sit in front of my keyboard, you know?
I'll take this.
Plus two damage for the room.
Doubles Isaac, I mean, whatever.
Another one?
Okay, imagine we double again and then again.
I mean, okay, that's pretty cool.
I shall take that.
Plus two damage for the room.
Yeah, I like.
We're also on a tight schedule here, so let's go.
No, take the pillow.
Dammit.
Okay, go!
Wish me luck!
We're gonna use a coupon here and have ultimate gains.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Yeah, my damage is pretty good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, you bastard, I didn't see that.
Very good.
Speed, decrease size, whatever.
Oh, wait.
No, no, that's good, that's good, that's good.
Oh!
We have access!
Oh, we gotta go in here first.
Make it free.
Take it.
Leave.
Oh, I can't leave.
What did I just get?
Headless baby.
Generous...
Okay, whatever.
Not super exciting.
Kinda underwhelming.
Wait.
Oh, it's here now!
Oh, here we go.
Boiled baby.
Sister Maggie.
Tooth and nail.
For six seconds, transform into a spiky statue for one second.
The statue form...
Or in the statue form.
Isaac is invincible to most forms of damage and deals 40 contact damage.
Wait, is this the one that goes...
Jim.
I like it.
Okay, we've got angels and we've got demons and everything else in between right here.
I call upon the devil to nail the angel.
Jim, Jim, Jim.
It's dark in here, this is gonna make things a little more challenging.
Especially for these guys that fly across the screen.
Did he just kill his friend?
That's awesome.
Oh man, I'm fast.
Okay, okay, not bad.
I need you to walk on my creep over here.
What is that sound?
Walk on my creep, baby.
Jim,
Jim, Jim.
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
That was sick.
Predictive bombing.
I'm so glad I got these hearts, man.
Imagine I had blue hearts now.
That would be a disaster.
Oh, that hit me.
What's this?
Uh...
Oh yeah, right, that guy.
Maybe I shouldn't have done that.
If I accidentally run into him, I think I'm gonna have a bad time.
Let me just do this.
Low him the fuck up.
Steven is here.
Very good.
Wow, you hit me.
Jim versus Steven.
Who's gonna win?
Oh my god.
I think this guy over here is mad.
What?
You little asshole.
I will not let that aggression stand.
The bird is helping so much.
Oh yeah, when he's feared, he's gonna jump away from me.
Dude, I love this room.
This is so much fun.
This one's gonna be tough.
What is even happening?
Well, you're gonna appear, okay.
I think I'll kill the blob first.
The jumping around is messing with me.
Ah, actually spiders.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Angel time!
That was sick.
I need to locate a heart.
There we go.
He's doing straight shots, yeah.
Again?
Wait, am I immune to that?
How come I didn't take damage?
Something's happening.
Oh, let's kill the small guy first, maybe.
We got a card here.
Justice.
Sure.
Like little flies like that need to die, because I can't see them and they're gonna hit me and it hurts.
You're gonna jump over there.
Where are you?
Okay, okay, okay.
Focus, focus, focus.
Yes, yes.
12 out of 15.
I'm being, I'm being gravitated.
The gravitation.
It's real.
It's mega real.
Nice.
Who are you?
Oh, you came from there.
I don't even look at what the enemies are nowadays.
I just shoot.
This guy's actually kind of tough.
Absolutely not.
Ah, you do lasers?
What the heck, man?
He jumps opposite where I'm going, it seems.
No, okay, well he's dead now.
What do we got now?
Okay, we got this guy floating around like a lizard on ice.
Okay, he wasn't too bad.
Where did he go?
This guy.
Which corner is he gonna go to, though?
Probably the top one, right?
Yeah, there he is.
Whoa, he's modified.
He's dead.
He's dead, baby!
Bozo!
Ah, soul heart, random chance to briefly apply fear or charm.
I mean, even more fear or charm?
I like it.
Chance to spawn a rainbow poop on the ground when taking damage.
Now, that's interesting.
All right, then.
Rainbow poop.
That was good.
That's a free item, pretty much.
Oh, I don't want free tears.
I mean, tears down.
I do want free tears.
Don't get me wrong.
Very good.
I mean, I just did 15 waves.
I think I can handle three.
My body is a fear-producing machine.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Sick.
Jera!
Please, we got to find a million blue hearts now, or black hearts.
Imagine.
Just imagine.
Hey, guys.
You seem to be stuck.
Yeah, kiss.
Oh, that was me.
That was a bomb.
I don't care.
I'm kind of going super fast here.
I'm doing it, mom.
Go!
The fallen.
I will make the devil deal free.
Mark my words.
Okay, then.
That was not good.
Are you got?
Yeah, here we go.
Multidimensional baby.
Oh, that's actually good.
I like this one.
Sick.
Okay, what are we going to get?
That one.
Yeah, let's turn them all into thingies.
Go ahead.
Cool.
And contract from below decreases the likelihood of a room clear reward.
Doubles the room.
Okay, you know what?
Let's try and take this for once.
See if it's actually good.
I feel like it's probably shit.
Wait, this is actually...
We exchange a red heart for a black heart.
Okay.
We'll do that.
Gives Isaac curse of the lost.
Hey, black heart!
I'll take that.
Fuck, I should have Jared in it!
I could have had Jared.
Oh, God, I had Jared.
Shit.
I could have had four black hearts instead of two.
If I've had the ability of, you know, looking into the future.
But I didn't.
Should have scripted today, man.
Why am I doing it live?
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God, I got it.
Careful now.
You're done.
Son.
Okay.
You know what?
Actually, I'm not too mad about that.
That speedrun strat's right there.
Wait, there didn't even point to going faster anymore.
I guess that's how another did open.
If you want to go even more crazy.
Honestly, I think I can do it again.
I can do it, like, they keep spawning hearts.
Oh, no, go this way.
That was close.
That was scary.
I don't think I've ever seen those enemies.
I have Jaira, I have Jaira, I have Jaira.
I'm strong and powerful.
Don't forget it.
We have Jaira.
Holy room.
Check this out.
I'm kind of in a...
Take me out of here.
That was amazing.
This way.
Jaira!
No.
It's horrible.
Please.
Boss spotted.
I'm going.
It lives.
Not for long.
You bastard.
Nose is itchy.
Okay.
Solid.
Kind of.
Three hearts.
Yeah.
You know, it's not fantastic.
Okay.
So what do we got here?
Dark bomb.
No.
Wait, actually.
No, no.
I'm good.
I'm good, bro.
Wait, I'm an idiot.
I've...
I'm not even gonna say it.
You know what it is.
Fucking hell.
Yeah.
I better not lose this now.
That's all I'm saying.
What even are these people?
Kind of undead bummer man.
Whoa.
Don't even.
Do odd.
Okay.
We're not going in there.
Speed, speed, speed, speed, speed.
Okay, Jera time.
Dude, what is this guy?
He's insane.
What?
Well, I think we're in trouble now.
What the fuck?
I'm fucking done with this challenge, dude.
Never again.
I hate it.
I hate this challenge so much.
I can't beat it.
It's too fucking hard.
Damn.
Oh.
I don't know how to do it.
I, legitimate, I don't know why this challenge is so difficult.
Like, I take any other character, I win easily.
This character, I just can't.
Wow.
Yeah, challenges are definitely challenging.
The next person who says I don't use my actives anymore, or it's, you know, enough.
I will ban them.
For 50 days.
And then I will mute you for 10 days.
I am aware of it!
I know my limitation, okay?
It pains nobody more than me.
Yeah, if you tell the truth, you get banned.
Only lies now, guys.
Come on, let me hear some lies.
Stop using your actives.
I will, thank you.
I think they actually hold me back.
They're definitely causing me to lose, if you've noticed.
You use your actives an amount that feels reasonable for the amount of experience you have.
Oh, wait, you're lying.
Ah, shit.
That was so good, though.
I would have taken that.
Damn it.
Oh, Mega Satan!
What the hell was that?
We gotta get back to Mega Satan.
We actually have to pick Magdalene and play her more, just because of that.
Mega Stan, yeah.
Mega Stanley found himself in front of two doors.
Please put Speed Runner Zazel into the next pole.
Hey, you want to see Speed Runner Zazel?
I'll provide it!
I love doing that.
Oh, yeah, Lazarus.
Oh, I forgot about Lazarus, you're right.
We should have done a Lazarus option on the pole.
Dude, Speed Runner Zazel is one of my favorite things in the game.
I love a Zazel.
I love going fast.
That's the best cocktail ever.
Delicious.
I've not played Darkest Dungeon.
You think I would like it?
I know it's a roguelike.
Jackie cam went...
You know what?
You would have gotten a lot out of that today, because she kept jumping up and trying to sit on my keyboard.
Which is weird, because she normally doesn't do it.
It's also her feeding time in, like, five minutes-ish.
Darkest is more extraction, though.
You mean, like, Tarkov extraction?
Okay, then I'm maybe not thinking of the same game you are.
D.D.'s awesome.
Okay.
There's a one and a two, right?
I guess I should play the first one first.
Can you make the Gym mod say Gym Gym instead of just Gym?
I need more Gyms.
I probably could.
Or maybe a randomized Gym.
Maybe it's like one, maybe it's three, maybe it's two.
We'd never know.
What is this Gym business?
It's just a reference to the Stanley Parable.
I'm not gonna say more than that.
It's a fun one.
You can try it.
The game is worth it.
Random pitch Gym.
Yeah, I like that one!
Just like the item I had today.
Gym, Gym, Gym!
Make Gym use Cauchy distribution for potentially unbound the number of Gyms.
I like the way you're thinking.
Yeah, we just ended the plans here.
I don't want to say that I rage quit, but I maybe rage quit a little bit.
Maybe there's 30% rage quit in this quit right here.
Super secret Stanley instead of Gym that happens to one in 100,000 Gyms.
Yes, that one.
What is Gym in Danish?
Gym, I think.
It's just a little shorter.
A little more pronounced.
Did you note anything interesting today?
Oh yeah, lots of stuff.
That lucky pillow run was insane, right?
Oh yeah, right, actually.
That was amazing.
I like the cut of your Gym, pal.
Wait, what is the original sentence there?
I like the cut of your... is it?
I like the cut of your Gym, normally?
Something like that, right?
Oh, Gym.
What is a Gym even?
Hold on.
Gym is a triangular sail that sets ahead of the formast of a sailing vessel.
Is that true?
Oh, I guess so.
I guess sailors would say that.
Hey, I like the cut of your Gym.
You really did scissor that one well, you know?
Well, there we go.
We all learned something new today.
How come we don't make up any more sayings nowadays?
We have all these amazing sayings from like a hundred years ago when people were out on the seas.
Sailing around or, you know, dealing with cows and pigeons and, you know, all that stuff.
We don't make those nowadays, do we?
Okay, but 6-7 is not the same thing.
It's not like an expression you use to convey something, is it?
It's also not as inventive, I don't think.
It is?
How?
Like, when would you use 6-7?
Okay, I see dead ass, but it's not really...
I wouldn't even say it's the same.
Maybe I'm just biased because I've been using those old expressions for so long.
Yeah, exactly.
Those are just words, not sayings.
Okay, do a barrel roll that one, I guess.
But that's more like a meme, right?
It's not something you would say to your friend, you know?
You go to the store and he gets a carton of milk.
And you go, hey, do a barrel roll!
And he goes, haha, good one.
That wouldn't make any sense to do, you know?
Cook is definitely a new one.
Yeah, okay, that one I like.
I like Cook.
Yeah, Cook is a good one.
Yeah, I would say memes are just jokes that are spread on the internet.
Usually involving a picture as well.
Hold my beer, that one, I guess.
That's true.
Yeah, that's the first one I've heard so far.
That makes sense.
Yeah, hold my beer, that's a good one.
Did you note about the hidden way onto the map?
No, I didn't, and now I'm not gonna note it.
I'm gonna remember it.
Oh, Jackie, what is going on with you?
Can you hear her?
Ah, you probably can, the music is playing.
Also, speaking of music.
Nah, it's okay.
Actually, I'm gonna go now.
I'm gonna feed Jackie.
I'm gonna see what the hell is going on with her.
She needs some attention.
I gotta play with her.
She needs some playtime.
Yeah, she wants attention.
Okay, guys, thank you for watching.
We're making progress.
We're seeing new things every single time I stream this game, which is blowing my mind, because we've been playing this game for 70, 80 hours.
What's happening, you know?
Pretty soon, we're done.
Love my work, see ya.